这你朋友吗
Is this your friend?
他叫什么名字
What's their name?
- 皱纹先生 - 皱纹先生
Mr. Wrinkles.  Mr. Wrinkles?
真是好名字呢
Well, that's a good name.
我叫里克
I'm Ric.
阿莉莎
Alyssa.
很高兴认识你  阿莉莎
It's nice to meet you, Alyssa.
你觉得你和皱纹先生
Now, do you think you and Mr. Wrinkles
要不要一起去旅行啊
would like to go on a trip?
但我家在这里啊
But I live here.
我知道的
I know. I know.
但我有一所学校  里面都是跟你一样特别的孩子
But I run a school for very special kids just like you,
我觉得你和皱纹先生
and I think that you and Mr. Wrinkles
会很喜欢那里的
would really like it there.
你想去看看吗
Do you want to visit?
要不要去
What do you say?
好的  走吧
Yeah? Okay. Let's go.
这边要怎么处理
What do you want to do about this?
你觉得如果是汽油泄露大家会相信吗
You think anyone will buy a gas leak?
我很厌烦自己  醒过来
* I'm so sick of me, wake up... *
你听说阿莉莎·常今天早干嘛了吗
Did you hear what Alyssa Chang did this morning?
乔西  丽兹  你们好
Hey, Josie, Lizzie.
你们的花花好漂亮啊
Your flowers are pretty.
我也想要一个
I want one.
抱歉  不过这是我们妈妈
Sorry, but our mom
给我们的
gave them to us.
行吧
Fine.
咒语
Pellis Tinctura.
阿莉莎·常又开始暴怒了
Alyssa Chang's on the warpath again.
赶紧躲开吧
Stay clear if you can.
你确定你准备好了吗
Are you sure you're ready for this?
这个古董是我们妈妈的
This artifact belonged to our mother.
她和她朋友用这个
She and her friends used it
准确的预测了
to perfectly predict
未来
the future.
乔西
Josie.
这个东西需要一点信息
The device requires knowledge.
你最喜欢的颜色  和一个数字
Your favorite color and number.
紫色  9
Purple and nine.
失败者
* Loser *
有时候我希望
* Some days I wish I's *
我是其他人
* Anyone else... *
古董发话了
And the artifact speaks.
你会成为一个巨魔
You will be a troll,
嫁给杰德
married to Jed,
住在垃圾桶里
and live in a garbage can.
我只想要
* I just want... *
不要让他们浪费你的时间
* Don't let 'em waste your time *
我才是最初的
* I'm the original *
失败者
* Loser... *
你们听说大新闻了吗
Did you guys hear the big news?
阿莉莎·常有室友了
Alyssa Chang has a roommate.
祝她幸福吧
Pray for her.
干什么啊
What the hell?
你瞎啊
Are you blind?
我不是给门把手下咒语  说请勿打扰了吗
I spelled the knob to "do not disturb."
我需要魔法化学课本
I need my chemistry of magic textbook.
还有  为什么在我床上搞
And more importantly, why are you on my bed?
我觉得要让你的床也见识见识床的意义啊
I thought it'd be nice if it saw some action.
抱歉  霍普
I'm sorry, Hope.
我去兰登那边睡了
I'm crashing at Landon's.
祝你们拉手愉快哦
Have fun holding hands.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
你觉得呢  皱纹先生
What do you think, Mr. Wrinkles?
我穿着比她穿着好看吧
Looks better on me than her, right?
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第10集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
好了
Okay,
够了
that's enough.
我们是想让这玩意不爆炸
We're trying to stop it from exploding,
而不是加速进程
not speed up the process.
翻 译  岛岛
我们已经试了12个咒语了
We have tried 12 different spells.
这
This is...
不是魔法能解决的问题了
not a problem that magic can fix.
那你的办法就比较好吗
Well, it's better than your solution
用水泥封起来
of covering it in concrete
翻 译  silver
然后扔到海里去
and dropping it in the ocean.
或许我就活该被黑魔法
Maybe I deserve the black magic
绕回来反噬我吧
to just boomerang back to me.
别对自己太苛刻了
Just cut yourself some slack, okay?
你犯了个错误而已
You made a mistake.
翻 译  JoaH
等等
Wait.
如果我们改良一下老爸的想法呢
What if we try Dad's idea, but better?
翻 译  晁安
我们不把这个破厄运沙漏扔进海里
Instead of dropping the discount lava lamp
而且扔到一个魔法无处可逃的地方
in the ocean, we drop it in a place where magic can't escape.
监狱世界
The prison world.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
不  这多完美啊
No, this is perfect.
今晚有个天体活动
There's a celestial event tonight.
有流星雨  我们不是正好需要这个
- A meteor shower-- and that is what we need
特效：小螺号
来让星位实现吗
to make the ascendant work, right?
对  还需要班尼特血
Yeah, that and Bennett blood.
我说了不行
No, I said no!
我会搞定的
I will figure this out.
校 对   岛岛
好吗
Okay?
我不在的时候
Don't do anything
特 效   麦 斯
别瞎搞
while I'm gone.
塞巴斯蒂安
It's bad enough
跟我玩消失就够烦人的了
that Sebastian ghosted me,
现在老爸还跟一个烦人的控制狂一样
but now Dad's acting like an annoying control freak.
他是不会让我们跟疯子叔叔凯一切
He's not gonna let us anywhere near that prison world
接近监狱世界的
with our psychotic Uncle Kai.
如果我们给送到一个不同的监狱世界呢
Then what if we send it to a different one?
搞一个新的星位  一个新的监狱世界
Make a new ascendant and a new prison world
没有什么杀人狂叔叔
with no homicidal uncles.
那需要很多魔法啊
It's gonna take a lot of magic.
我们五岁的时候就做到了啊
We did it when we were five.
那是跟邦妮阿姨一起啊  我们自己做不到的
With Aunt Bonnie. I mean, we can't do this alone.
那我去找个人
Then I'll find someone.
能有多难吗
How hard could it be?
有点重了
Okay, that was a little hard.
我先说好啊
Okay, um, to be clear,
我说让你训练我  是训练小白的意思
when I asked for training, I sort of meant for beginners.
嗯
Yeah.
抱歉啊
Sorry.
我就是快被阿莉莎·常气死了
It's just, Alyssa Chang has me all worked up.
那姐们完全做事没有分寸
That girl has no boundaries.
各种乱拿我东西
She takes all of my stuff
每天都要点一个新的香味蜡烛
and every day she has a new scented candle.
其中有一个还是培根味道的
One of which that smelled like bacon.
我感觉她是想把我逼走
I think she's trying to gaslight me.
是啊  欺负人的人都那么干
Yeah, bullies'll do that.
相信我  我可是很有经验的
Trust me, I pretty much have a PhD on the subject.
她都让我开始怀念把怪物
She makes me long for the days when I could toss a monster
扔到马里之洼的日子了
into the Malivore pit.
虽然这个建议
Well, I know this might not sound
感觉没有那么激动人心  但
like the most action-packed advice, but, um...
你可以试着跟她谈谈啊
maybe just try talking to her.
恶霸们都不喜欢跟人正面刚
Bullies hate being confronted.
可以试试啊  科比博士
I guess I could try that, Dr. Kirby.
太好了
Great.
要不再来练练吧
Uh, how about some more sparring first?
来点柔道或者格斗啥的
Maybe some judo or kenpo?
- 或者合气道呢  - 还是从最基本的左勾拳开始吧
Aikido? Why don't we start with a basic jab?
让你能慢慢的而不是一下子就陷入危险之中
Have you walking instead of running head first into danger.
绝对是很危险的
It's definitely dangerous.
这可是个莫拉·米希拉姆
It's a Mora Miserium.
如果碎掉了  所有的黑魔法都会进入乔西体内的
If it shatters, all the black magic goes into Josie.
给我吧
Oh, and, here...
我不知道这种东西还存在呢
I didn't know those still existed.
更别提怎么修复了
Let alone how to repair one.
- 不过我去查查 - 艾玛
But... let me have... Emma.
多利安
Dorian.
你们俩聊吧
I'm gonna let you two catch up.
我去找一个拆弹专家
I've got to find myself a bomb expert.
你来了啊
You're in town.
里克让我来帮忙操持女巫集会日
Ric asked me to run Coven Day.
你从日本飞过来就为了女巫集会日吗
You flew from Japan for Coven Day?
对啊
Of course.
有什么问题吗
Why wouldn't I?
很多年来  女巫们都因为与众不同
For years, witches have been persecuted
甚至被误认为危险  而遭到迫害
for being different, even dangerous.
女巫集会日是一个让我们所有人
Coven Day is an opportunity for all of us to celebrate
可以庆祝  并且自豪的做一名女巫的日子
and to take pride in being a witch.
也是让我们学习不同女巫集会
To learn about the individual covens
如何组成魔法大社区的好机会
that make up our magical community.
你见到阿莉莎·常了吗
Hey, uh, have you seen Alyssa Chang?
今天没见到
No, not today.
很开心你决定加入我们了
Glad you decided to join us.
抱歉  我真的很不想来的
Sorry, I just really didn't want to be here.
我们等会说
We'll talk later.
其他人  好好享受吧
For the rest of you, enjoy.
你会发现女巫集会日  是一个有付出
You'll find that what you get out of Coven Day
就会有回报的日子
is what you put into it.
嘿
Hi.
我知道咱俩互相有点看不顺眼
Now, I know we don't see eye-to-eye,
你肯定也完全不想
and I'm sure you probably weren't super excited
有一个室友
about having a roommate.
我是不介意有室友的
Oh, I don't mind having a roommate.
我只是不喜欢你
I just don't like you.
好吧
Okay.
我们可以聊一下分寸的问题吧
Maybe we could talk about boundaries.
从头来过
Start over.
她把一切都怪到你头上呢
She's blaming you for everything.
如果你不把她弄走
They're going
他们就会把你弄走的
to get rid of you unless you get rid of her.
你说得对  我们应该重新开始
You're right. We should start over.
回到我自己一个住房间的时候
Back to when I had the room to myself.
欢迎大家听我演讲
Uh, welcome to my presentation.
我应该聊我的巫师团的
I'm supposed to talk about my coven,
但我没有
but I don't have one.
我也一直好奇我这么格格不入的原因
And I've always wondered why I don't fit in
或者为什么我魔法用的这么烂
or why I'm bad at magic...
因为你被这里录取是因为记录错误吗
Because you got admitted here due to a clerical error?
但我研究了一下  我觉得我有答案了
But I've done some research and I think I have an answer.
我被误诊了了
I've been misdiagnosed.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
我不是巫师
I'm not a witch, I'm...
我是仙子
a fairy.
我知道有这种东西的
I know it's out there, um...
但是
but...
仙子们喜欢蜂蜜
fairies enjoy honey,
很整洁
they're incredibly tidy,
还喜欢唱歌
and they love to sing.
就跟我一样
Uh, just like me.
我还
Uh, I also...
没有父母
never knew my parents,
估计他们是被马里之洼吃掉了把
so maybe they were eaten by Malivore.
或许你也该被马里之洼吃掉   这样我们就不用
Maybe you could be eaten by Malivore so we can forget
继续听你在这哔哔了
your whole presentation.
有没有看到
Does-does anyone else see...?
你浪费了仙子的地方吗
A waste of fairy space?
你要留堂了  阿莉莎
That's detention, Alyssa.
你是这儿老师吗
Do you even work here?
今天是
I do today.
行吧
Fine.
- 也没什么比这更糟的事了 - 那可没准
It couldn't be worse than this. I don't know.
比如跟你共处一室吗
Being alone in a room with you?
作为你的室友  简直是生不如死啊
As your roommate, that sounds like hell.
很好  霍普
Good, Hope.
不要让任何人把你变得软弱
Don't let anyone make you look weak.
嘿
Hey.
鞋子好看
Cute shoes.
我穿着更好看
They'd look better on me.
你跟阿莉莎·常怎么样了
Hey. How'd it go with Alyssa Chang?
你们成为好闺蜜了吗
You guys BFFs?
你保护不了他的
You cannot protect him.
先离开他
Get rid of him
省的你失去他
before you lose him.
你的建议完全没用  兰登  就跟你这人一样
Your advice was useless, Landon, just like you.
嘿  韦德
Hey, Wade.
虽然我也一直都很喜欢
Uh, you know I'm always down for more adventures
勇士马格努斯和妖怪格纳什的故事
of Magnus the Warrior and G'nash the Bugbear,
但我现在真的有点紧急情况啊
but I got an emergency brewing here.
你这跟霍普表现的跟阿莉莎·常的升级版一样
Does it have anything to do with Hope acting
有关系吗
like Alyssa Chang 2.0?
我有个想法呢
'Cause I've got a theory.
没错  快来  你发现什么了
Ding, ding. Get in here. What do you got?
这是一个卡里恩
We're dealing with a Qareen.
这是一个阿拉伯怪物  会跟人耳语灌输不安全感
It's an Arabian monster that whispers insecurities
并且通过大家不合来饱餐
and feeds off discord.
它的超能力是让大家生气吗
Its superpower is making people angry?
他是通过冲突进食的
Uh, it feeds off the strife,
变得越来越强大  就能影响越来越多人
becoming stronger and affecting more and more people
直到他变得具体化出现在我们之间
until it materializes into our plane.
现在还不成型
Right now it's out of phase.
不可见  不可触摸
It's invisible and intangible.
马里之洼的入口不是关闭了吗
I thought the Malivore portal is closed.
不是吗
I mean, isn't it?
我不知道那玩意怎么来的
I don't know how it got here,
但绝对是真实的
but it's definitely real.
我看到了
I saw it.
你不是说是无形的吗
You said it's invisible.
仙子是能看到的
Not to fairies.
所以
So...
我们要试一试
we are going to try
冥想练习
a meditative exercise
来舒缓我们的神经
to calm our nerves...
他们都太软弱了
They are so soft.
只有你可以保护他们所有人
Only you can protect them all.
得了吧  受了点伤就来干这个啊
Really? Some hurt feelings, and this is what we're doing?
怪不得所有事情都要我自己来干
It's no wonder I have to do everything myself.
看来这个练习对我们其中某些人
Sounds like this will be especially helpful
会格外有帮助呢
for some of us.
大家闭上眼睛
Now close your eyes.
专注于自己的呼吸
Focus on your breathing...
拥抱寂静
...and embrace the silence.
艾玛  能来一下吗
Emma, could I borrow you for a sec?
我们正有事呢
We're in the middle of something.
我也有事  而且我的事情可不包括
So am I, and my thing doesn't include,
围成一圈神神道道的
like, "Kum-Bah-Yah" circle time.
坐下
Sit.
你和你妹妹应该一开始就来的
You and your sister should have been here from the start.
再来  闭上眼睛
Again. Eyes closed.
专注于寂静
Focus on the silence.
谢谢
Thank you.
我已经试过一切了
I've tried everything.
冷冻住  封在水泥里
Freezing it, covering it in concrete,
拆开来  都不管用
defusing it. Nothing works.
如果这炸弹爆炸了
And if this bomb goes off,
会毁灭一切的
it will destroy everything.
- 感觉不好弄啊  - 是啊
Sounds intense. Yeah.
我以为你是在写真实犯罪故事啊
But I thought you wrote true crime.
现在这个类别的小说市场还挺火爆的
Well, you know, the genre market's hot right now.
懂了
Gotcha.
那为什么不让你的角色把炸弹引爆呢
Uh, so why don't you just have your character blow up the bomb?
因为这个角色非常急迫的
Because the character's desperately trying
不想让炸弹爆掉
to keep it from exploding.
其实对于任何爆炸物来说  这就是一般的
Actually, that's the general render-safe protocol
安全流程啊
for any explosive.
远距离引爆
Detonate it from a distance.
如果没有一个足够的安全距离呢
Well, what if there isn't a safe distance?
我们爆炸品处理局就是这么办事的
That's how we did things in the EOD.
不过既然是小说  就瞎编呗
But it's fiction; you can just make something up, right?
太好了
Great.
伊森把自己搞得留堂了
Ethan landed himself in detention.
他又跟一个恶霸干起来了
Apparently, he fought another bully.
伊森是个好孩子啊
Well, listen, Ethan's a good kid,
他肯定是替跟弱小的人出头了
so I'm sure he was sticking up for someone smaller.
但我也不是校长了
But, look, I am not the principal anymore.
说实话  我倒希望丽兹和伊森这种孩子在一起呢
And to be honest, I wish Lizzie would date somebody like Ethan.
那个帅气的交换生呢
What happened to the good-looking exchange student?
塞巴斯蒂安
Yeah, Sebastian...
不太适合她
he's not right for her.
我得跟他说清楚的
And I had to let him know that.
我敢肯定  就跟所有青少年一样
But I'm sure, like every teenager,
他肯定是很理智的接受了你的建议呢
he was reasonably accepting of your point of view.
差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
天啊  里克  你干嘛了  把他杀了啊
Geez, Ric, what'd you do, murder him?
我要回答问题之前
Well, you're gonna have to get me a lawyer
你得给我找个律师啊  警长
before I answer that question, Sheriff.
闭上眼睛
Eyes closed.
专注于寂静
Focus on the silence.
咒语
Cessabit orbis.
我召唤了一个球体出来
I've summoned a sphere.
这代表着你们所有人的思想
It represents your collective thoughts
和情绪
and emotions.
我们的目标是保持这个球一直是绿色的
Our goal is to keep it a calm green that represents
也就代表着祥和宁静的心态
serenity and peace of mind.
她在利用你
She's using you.
我知道你只是利用我做神秘动物学的作业
I know you're just using me for cryptozoology homework.
他们在背后说你坏话
They talk behind your back.
我  我知道是你背着我乱说
Me? I know that you're the one talks behind my back.
你们的负能量思想污染了球体
Your negative thoughts are polluting the sphere,
改变了它的颜色
changing its color.
用心  女巫们
Focus, witches.
他们批判你
They judge you,
他们并不比你好
but they're not better than you.
告诉他们啊
Tell them.
我不知道什么更可悲了
I don't know what's worse,
是霍普抢走了乔西的傻缺男友
Hope stealing Josie's loser boyfriend, or Lizzie
还是丽兹被塞巴斯蒂安甩了  那哥们从1509年
getting dumped by Sebastian when she's the only girl
开始就没见过女的了
he's met since 1509.
如果你对他来说足够了
If you were enough,
他也不会离开你
he wouldn't have left.
告诉他们你是值得的
Show you're enough.
至少我还有个家
At least I have a family,
不像你  一个孤儿
unlike you, orphan.
咒语
Incendia.
我服了你了  你真的很婊
I can't believe it--you are such a bitch.
你闭嘴吧
Shut your mouth.
够了
That's enough.
所有人都回房间冷静一下
Everyone, go to your rooms and cool off.
丽兹  丽兹
Lizzie, Lizzie.
哪里不对劲
Something's wrong.
我告诉你哪里不对
I will tell you what is wrong, okay.
你的头发  你的衣服
That hair. That shirt.
啊好吧
Oh, okay.
我明白了  你说的有道理
I see you have a point there.
怎么会这样呢
What is going on?
看我  多管闲事的哥们  我知道你很没家教
Look here, uh, Snoopy, I know you haven't been housebroken,
但你给我让开
but I'm gonna need you to get out of my way.
不然呢  要跟我斗舞吗
Or what, you gonna challenge me to a dance-off?
呵呵  小狼  给你扔个球去捡吧
Ah, very funny, wolf. Let's go play fetch.
-  怎么着  比划比划啊  - 来啊  谁怕谁啊
You want to go? You want to go? We can go. Let's do it.
来啊  来啊  揍我啊
We can do this... Bring it. Bring it, vamp.
来啊
Bring it. I'll do it.
你知道她没办法适应的
You knew she'd have problems adjusting.
已经很多年了  艾玛
It's been years, Emma.
她还是一直跟其他孩子
And she's still prone to getting in fights
找茬吵架
with the other kids.
我们之前也处理过问题学生
Look... we have dealt with problem students in the past.
我也不想这样  但如果她一直不改
I hate to say it, but if she keeps this up,
我们可能得考虑退学了
we might have to consider expulsion.
我们说好了不再这样了的  里克
We said we'd never do that again, Ric.
我知道  但如果我们错了呢
I know, but... what if we were wrong?
怎么错了
Which way?
- 我看不到了  跟丢了 - 什么丢了
I can't see it. I lost it. Lost what?
兰登的时尚品味吗
Landon's fashion sense?
抱歉  我不是故意的
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
你说我的打扮很经典的
You said my look was classic.
你竟然也信
And you believed that?
抱歉  吧
Sorry... I think.
我真是生活在谎言之中
Well, I'm living a lie.
我们在找卡里恩
We're looking for the Qareen.
是一个怪物  让每个人都变得
It's a monster that makes everyone act like...
像你
You.
是隐形的  只有仙子才能看到
It's invisible; only fairies can see it.
你想吐槽他们  还是我来
Do you want to take this, or should I?
这都没啥好吐槽的
It's too easy.
吐槽了我都不会觉得有趣呢  抱歉了
Can't even get any pleasure out of it. Sorry.
大家注意力都集中一点  它的力量每时每刻都在增强
Hey, focus. It's gaining strength by the minute.
一旦它足够强大
Once it's strong enough
就可以在一个没有仙子的地方出现了
to manifest itself on a, um, non-fairy plane...
不管怎样  我们得想个办法阻止它
Anyway, we have to figure out a way to stop it.
每次你说些鼓舞士气的话时就没那么帅了
It is so much less impressive when you give the hero speeches.
而我就很帅气
That was all me.
好吧  计划是什么
Okay, what's the plan?
然后我回到家
Then I get back home,
玛雅故意表现得很好
and Maya is on her best behavior.
所以就算你不是警察也能意识到
And you do not have to be a cop to realize...
- 她在隐瞒什么  - 可不是
That she's hiding something.Yeah.
这时我听到客厅里有声音
That's when I hear a noise in the living room.
我打开壁橱门发现
I open the closet door to find...
让我猜猜  一个漂亮姑娘
Let me guess. It's a girlfriend.
我倒希望如此呢  其实是个像是小丑花车的东西
I wish. It was like a clown car in there.
五个孩子在里面  还有一个桶
Five kids, one keg.
我都不知道他们是怎么挤进去的
I don't even know how they all squeezed in there.
有意思  那你接下来都做了些什么
Yikes. So, what'd you do next?
我的第一反应是把他们铐起来
Mm... my first instinct was to cuff them
拖到警察局去
and drag them all down to the station.
但后来我冷静了下来  做了一件普通父母
But then I calmed down and I did the reasonable thing
都应该做的事  因为
that we always do, because...
这就是我们都应该做的不是吗
that's what we have to do, right?
我对我的女儿撒谎  瞒了她们很多事情  以此来保护她们
I-I lie to my girls and keep secrets to protect them,
所以我不确定我是不是
so I'm not sure I'm the right person to be asking
征求父母意见的合适人选
for parental advice.
我都有点绝望了
Well, I'm a little desperate.
我的乖孩子又跟别人打架了
My good kid just got in another fight.
我支持伊森  所以
I'm Team Ethan, so...
我相信他自己能做出正确的决定
maybe trust him to make the right decisions on his own.
那么有时也许你应该让你的女儿
Then perhaps you should let your daughters
自己解决自己的问题
solve their own problems sometime.
如果让别人  就说警察好了  听到你保守的这些秘密
And would it absolve you of your own sins to let someone--
这样会不会帮你赎罪呢
- say, a cute cop-- hear these secrets that you're keeping?
哦  抱歉了  警官
Oh, sorry, Sheriff.
我就算死也不会说出这些秘密的
But I'll be taking those secrets with me to the grave.
我就问你一个问题
I asked you a simple question.
- 为什么所有事情到你这儿都成了秘密  - 你还说我
Why does everything have to be a secret with you?Me?
至少我可以敞开心扉
: Oh. At least I can open up.
而你从来没有真实地表达过你的想法
You're never emotionally available.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
真实表达我的想法  你可是都在日本找了份工作的
Emotionally available? You took a job in Japan!
你从没告诉过我你是怎么想的
And you never told me how that made you feel.
怎么了
What?
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that thing?
是这样的
Okay.
卡里恩确实有一个致命的弱点
The Qareen does have an Achilles' heel.
他的弱点是
Uh, it's weak
没药  辛巴达的弯刀  还有仙子
to myrrh, Sinbad's scimitar, and fairies.
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
- 你为什么就是不相信我  - 你会飞
Why don't you believe me? Can you fly
会射出仙尘  会让别人感到快乐吗
or shoot fairy dust or make others gleeful?
不会  因为你做的事情和
No. Because you're doing the exact same thing
兰登训练时做的完全一样
that Landon is with his training:
你只是在努力适应
you're trying to fit in.
你这就是异想天开
It's delusional.
我说的有点重了
I sh-shouldn't have said that.
你知道我训练的目的是
You do know the reason I'm training is to help you
帮你做这些事吗
with this stuff?
如果我需要有人死得很惨
If I need someone to die a lot,
或者被人欺负  我知道该给谁打电话
or be picked on, I know who to call.
韦德,我很抱歉  真的
Wade, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我本意并非如此
I didn't mean that--I didn't mean that.
你是该感到抱歉
Actually, you did.
卡里恩放大了不安全感
The Qareen magnifies insecurities.
你的话会更让他们感到不安
It doesn't make them.
书呆子们
Hey, book nerds.
校园里出现了个怪物
There's a monster on campus.
那玩意儿有点像霍普上星期长的痘痘
It kind of looks like that pimple Hope had last week.
你确定那不是你自己的映象吗
Are you sure it wasn't your own reflection?
真好  你的话太能
Great. It's strong enough
- 鼓舞人心了  - 好吧  我们得把你送到
to be on our plane. Okay, well, we need to get you
安全的地方  以防万一
somewhere safe just in case.
这样你就不会再被绑架了
So you don't go get yourself kidnapped again.
我真的不是在责怪受害者
I'm really not blaming the victim here.
其实我感觉它不是在追我
I actually don't think it's after me.
它会主动避开韦德和我
Like, it actively avoided Wade and me.
那它想要什么
Then what does it want?
这不会有用的  丽兹
This isn't gonna work, Lizzie.
在克拉克那件事之后  我甚至连
After what happened with Clarke, I'm nervous to do
最小的咒语都不敢施
even the smallest spells...
担心魔法会适得其反
worried that the magic's gonna backfire.
别把它摔碎
Don't let it break.
乔西  快醒醒  乔
Josie, wake up. Jo!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
怎么回事
What happened?
是魔鬼
Monster.
艾玛施了个障碍咒
Uh, Emma put up a barrier spell,
这样就可以把卡里恩困在这里了
so the Qareen's stuck in here with us.
- 它把沙漏拿走了  - 沙漏
It took the Sandclock.The Sandclock?
- 为什么啊  - 这不重要
Why?It doesn't matter.
我们得把它拿回来
We just need to get it back.
我们一定能把它拿回来的
We can take this thing out, okay?
我们三个可是最屌的女巫
We are three badass witches
外带一个渣渣菜鸟
and one moderately competent bird.
如果沙漏碎了
Except if the Sandclock gets damaged,
非常糟糕的事情就会发生
something really bad is gonna happen.
我们需要利用一个弱点来迅速击垮它
We need to exploit a weakness to take it down fast.
就希望兰登对它弱点的研究
Except Landon's research into that
能和他的战斗技能一样有用
was about as useful as his fighting skills.
天啊  我说错话了
Oh, my God, sorry.
- 爱你  -  或者也许我的研究没什么问题
Love you.Or maybe my research was fine,
但上帝却禁止你用你的大脑
but God forbid you use your brain
来解决问题
instead of punching every problem.
老天  我怎么也变成这样了
Oh, crap. I'm infected.
你也没能幸免啊
Join the club.
看来魔鬼雨露均沾啊
Maybe the only one that'll have you.
抱歉了  魔鬼
Sorry. Monster.
为什么我现在会受到影响  我以前还没有
Why am I being affected now? I wasn't before.
我可能有了个主意
Okay. I might have a plan.
当时发生了什么
What happened back there,
大家说了什么
what everyone said,
都完全是不对的
it wasn't cool.
我们真的需要你的帮助来阻止卡里恩
And we really need your help to stop the Qareen.
怎么会呢  就像霍普说的  我就是个废物
Why? I'm useless, like Hope said.
那是因为仙子们掌控着信任的力量
That's because fairies run on belief.
我研究过了  越多的人相信你
I did some research, and the more people that believe in you,
你的力量就会越强大
the stronger your powers.
没人相信我
No one believes in me.
我相信你
I do.
是你第一个看到了卡里恩
You saw the Qareen first.
你不会受到它的力量的影响  当我
You were unaffected by its powers, and when I was
和你在一块时  卡里恩就无法影响我
hanging out with you, the Qareen couldn't infect me.
我百分之百相信你
I'm 100% behind you.
而且还不止我一人
And I'm not alone.
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
大家是在喊我的名字吗
Are people calling my name?
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
等会儿  我们在这干啥来着
Wait, why are we doing this again?
应该是有人过生日啥的
I think it's someone's birthday.
好吧
Oh.
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
我们把能召集的人都找来了
We gathered everyone we could.
把仙子放出来吧
Let loose the fairy.
你一定可以的  韦德
You got this, Wade.
大家都挺你
Just know that everyone believes in you.
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade!
有什么问题吗
Wh-Wha-What's wrong?
这样还是无法让我具有任何能力
This isn't giving me any powers.
我觉得大家不是真的相信我
I don't think anyone really believes in me.
这就是为什么我们不让布偶娃娃来执行我们的计划
This is why we don't entrust plans to Muppet Babies.
- 我才不会说抱歉呢  - 我相信你
I'm not sorry.I believe.
我会向你证明的
And I'll prove it.
你干嘛呢
What the hell are you doing?
证明我真的相信韦德
Trusting in Wade.
等等  我们不能打破沙漏
Wait, we can't break the Sandclock.
你就是个弱鸡
You're weak.
你连自己都保护不了  更别说保护别人了
You can't protect yourself, let alone anyone else.
闭上你的臭嘴吧  你才是弱鸡
Shut up. You're weak.
- 兰登  - 霍普  别冲动
Landon!Hope, stay calm.
我有能力了  霍普
I got this, Hope.
是兰登给予了我力量
Landon made sure of it.
这老弟就像个精灵一样
Oh. Dude's, like, all fairy.
简直就像真的一样
Like, for real.
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade! Wade!
韦德  韦德  韦德
Wade! Wade! Wade!
- 天哪  - 韦德
- Oh, my gosh!- Wade!
丽兹严重烧伤马上被送到医院去了
Lizzie was rushed to the infirmary with severe burns.
谢天谢地现在她没事了
Now, thankfully, she'll be okay.
- 我整个早上都在图书馆  - 我知道
Well, I was in the library all morning.I know.
我也知道你一直在练习连接咒
I also know you've been practicing linking spells.
将人与物体连接起来
Connecting people with objects.
抱歉  阿莉莎
I'm sorry, Alyssa.
但我不得不要把你送走了
But I'm gonna have to send you away.
我要被送到哪里去
Where am I gonna go?
如果还有其他选择呢
What if there was another option?
我可以施一个咒语来消除你做过的事的记忆
I can cast a spell to remove the memories of what you did.
还有对你父母遭遇的记忆
What happened with your parents.
你会有一个全新的开始
It could give you a fresh new start.
她跟其他人不一样
She's not like the others.
你怎么想  阿莉莎
What would you like to do, Alyssa?
我想待在这儿
I want to stay.
我还是不喜欢这个法子
I still don't like this idea.
大家都不喜欢  但这是我们唯一的办法了
None of us like it, but it's the only plan that we have.
在厄运沙漏再次破裂之前
And we have to do something
我们得做些什么
before the fishbowl of doom fractures again.
等等  时间间隙
Wait. "Time fractures."
那个预言
The prophecy.
你说的对
You're right.
我们得马上行动了
We've got to get a move on this now.
等等  你是打算让我们来做吗
Wait, you're letting us do this?
那个  我的炸弹专家
Well, m-my bomb expert--
她虽然没有在炸药方面
she didn't give me the best advice
给我好的建议  但她
on explosives, but she did
可是告诉我该怎么样让你们这些女孩
point out that I could be better at letting you girls
处理好你们自己的问题
solve your own problems.
我有点喜欢这个神秘的拆弹专家了
I like this mysterious demolition expert.
她叫什么
Does she have a name?
你们能搞定吗
Are you sure you guys can handle this?
孤身奋战可不行  但我们有伙伴
Not alone, but we have help.
大家凝聚一起
Working together.
这才是女巫集会日存在的意义
That's what Coven Day is all about.
只有女巫独身一人时
It's only when witches are alone
才是危险所在
that we're truly in danger.
但当我们聚集在一起时我们就是最强大的
But together we are strong and can cast spells that none of us
我们可以施展无人能施展的咒语
would be able to do ourselves.
我为我之前说过的话道歉
I'm sorry about what I said before.
你知道的  那个怪物
You know, the monster...
我自作自受
I deserved it.
我该试着去拒绝那个混蛋的蛊惑的
I'm gonna try to turn down the jerk.
对不起  我把你也牵扯进来了
I'm sorry for dragging us into this.
对不起  我竟然不知道你需要帮助
I'm sorry I didn't know you needed help.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
现在  女巫们  把注意力集中于这些碎片的组装上
Now, witches, focus on assembling these pieces
移动到一个新的星位上
into a new ascendant that will lead
然后引导其开启一个新的监狱世界
to a new prison world.
一个咒语成功了
One spell down.
准备下一个
One to go.
干得漂亮  女巫们
Well done, witches,
做的好
well done,
但还没有结束
but it's not over.
我们必须齐心协力
We must pull together
把我们的能量凝聚成一个整体
and channel our energy as one
在沙漏破碎之前把它放逐进去
to banish the Sandclock before it breaks.
我们必须要团结一致  对吧
We all got to stick together, right?
咒语
Sangiema Meam
Et Nos Mundo Carcerema.
咒语
Sangiema Meam
Et Nos Mundo Carcerema.
咒语
Sangiema...
我们做到了  结束了
We did it. It's gone.
谢谢
Thank you.
那一拳可真的打出去了
That jab is really coming along.
我有个好老师
I have a good teacher.
你的那种冲动  然后
* You get that rush and then... *
早些时候  我说了些
Earlier, I-I said some things...
我们都被怪物蛊惑了  把那些忘了吧
We both had monster brain. We can forget all about that.
我做不到
I can't. Um...
虽然很伤人
As much as it hurts...
但我说的都是真的
Um, what I said was true.
这只会让我更想要你
* It made me just want you more *
上天啊  你的爱
* My God, your love... *
听着
Look, um...
我爱你  兰登
I love you, Landon.
我恨你已不在
* And I hate that you're gone... *
我爱你难以承受打击的样子
I love that you can't take a punch.
我爱你靠智慧赢得胜利的样子
I love that you won today using brain,
即便你没有强健的肌肉
not brawn,
我爱你努力想变好的样子
and I love that you're always trying to be better.
但是
But, um,
我并不奢求你去做英雄
I don't want you to be the hero.
英雄永远不会被遗忘  但你也一样的
Th-The hero's never the one that's left standing.
从你爱情的废墟中重生  我会去
* From the rubble of your love, I'm gonna be... *
我不会再训练你让你和我对打了
I'm not gonna train you to fight with me anymore.
你曾经以为我是
* You ever thought I was... *
即便怪物再回来了也不会了
Not if the monsters are back.
每次你离开  我都倍感空虚
* Each time you left, there was a hunger *
好吧  但我不会停下来的
Well, I'm not stopping.
我感觉自己好像快死了
* I felt so dead... *
要是你不训练我的话  那我就去找个愿意训练我的人
If you won't train me, I'll find someone who will,
所以我们都站在了终点上
so that we're both standing at the end of this.
我从未注意到
* I never noticed *
我也会变得如此之强
* I'm gonna be stronger *
比你想象的还要更甚
* Than you ever thought I was. *
嘿  嗯  我
Hey, yeah, I...
我打来是想谢谢你之前给我提的建议
I just wanted to thank you for your advice earlier.
你的小说写完了吗
You finished your novel?
没
No.
我让我女儿们处理了这件事
I let my daughters take care of the situation,
令人惊讶的是  这个世界还好好的
and, shockingly, the world didn't end.
所以  算我欠你一次
So... I owe you one.
嘿
Hey, uh,
这周末一起吃晚饭怎么样
what do you say--dinner this weekend?
我的回答就在你口袋里
My answer's in your pocket.
你不去庆祝一下吗
Shouldn't you be celebrating?
你的法子奏效了
Your plan worked.
是啊  但是闹剧解决了
Yeah, but with the drama over,
我也找不出其他东西分散我的注意力了
I don't have anything to distract myself anymore.
分散啥注意力
Distract you from what?
想他也没关系的
It's okay to miss him.
我知道我不该想他
I know I shouldn't care.
塞巴斯蒂安虽然不是个好人  但是
Sebastian wasn't a great guy, but still...
悲伤的团队里能给我留个位子吗
Um, got room for one more in the cry pile?
我想兰登肯定很恨我
I think Landon might hate me.
你看起来很开心啊  阿莉莎
You look very happy, Alyssa, and I hear
我听说你还交到了朋友
you're making friends.
佐伊跟我说  我是她最好的朋友
Zoe told me that I'm her best friend.
- 那她是你的好朋友吗  - 她或者克拉拉吧
- Is she your best friend? - Either her, or maybe Clara.
这是个好问题
Well, that's a good problem to have.
对于你取得的进步我很骄傲
I'm so proud of the progress you've made,
所以我想
which is why I think
我们可以停止每周的训练了
we can stop having our weekly sessions.
真的吗  我已经可以了吗
Really? I'm better?
我觉得是的
I think so.
你怎么想
What do you think?
好
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
我想为之前的事道歉
I wanted to apologize for earlier.
就都怪到卡里恩身上就好了
Let's chalk it up to the Qareen.
不  在那之前
No, before that.
你在镇上这本不关我的事的
It's none of my business why you're in town.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
但今天我意识到
But today made me realize that...
我也应该更信任你一点的
I should be more honest with you.
我来镇里不是为了女巫集会日
I'm not in town for Coven Day.
里克请我帮他教导一个学生
Ric asked me to help him with a student.
有人给了他丢了一个
Someone who was giving him...
大麻烦
trouble.
你做了什么  艾玛
What did you do, Emma?
我们之前做过的
What we did before.
我来的时间是不是不对
Bad time?
不  我准备走了
No, I-I was just leaving.
我们晚点再谈
We'll discuss this later.
我记得我早些时候让你过来
I know I ordered you here earlier,
但很显然卡里恩影响了你
but it's clear the Qareen was influencing you,
我们都被影响了
well, all of us.
我不是想聊这些
That's not what I wanted to chat about.
我是想坦白一件事
I wanted to confess something.
你做了什么
What did you do?
不是我做了什么
It's not about what I did.
而是我知道你做了什么
It's what I know about what you did.
乔西最近施了这个净化咒
Josie recently did this purge spell
让每个人都记起霍普
to return everyone's memories about Hope,
但我想起的不止是关于霍普的事情
but Hope's not the only thing I remembered.
我还想起了其他事情
I remembered other things,
比如你对我做了什么
like what you did to me
还有萨尔茨曼博士对其他孩子做了什么
and what Dr. Saltzman did to those other kids.
你肯定很疑惑
This must be very confusing for you,
但我可以解释  我们去找萨尔茨曼博士
but I can explain. Let me go and get Dr. Saltzman.
这不可能了
That won't be possible.
你做了什么  阿莉莎
What did you do, Alyssa?
我把他们都送走了
I sent them away...
就像你送走其他人一样
just like you sent the others.
我想这才是理想中的赏罚分明
I thought it was poetic justice.
这不可能
That's not possible.
你需要正确的星位和班尼特的血才能做到的
You'd need the ascendant and Bennett blood.
也或者我只需要施一个连接咒
Or I would just need to use a linking spell.
这个机会我已经等了好几个星期了
I've been waiting for an opportunity for weeks.
看着萨尔茨曼一家抱怨着他们的生活
Watching the Saltzmans as they complained about their lives,
只担心他们自己
worried only about themselves.
然后  当所有人都沉浸在女巫集会日的喜悦中时
And then, when everyone else was basking in Coven Day bliss,
我把两个星位连接了起来
I linked the two ascendants.
当女孩们送沙漏的时候
When the girls sent the Sandclock,
她们也把自己和萨尔茨曼博士送了进去
they were also sending themselves and Dr. S.
我还增加了一个时间延迟的咒语
I added a time delay spell
所以没人知道到底发生了什么
so no one would realize what happened
直到为时已晚
until it was too late.
这个你可以感谢瓦尔德莫斯
You can thank Vardemus for that one.
你起来
Get up.
- 我们得把他们带回来  - 怎么带
- We're bringing them back.- How?
流星雨已经结束了
The meteor shower's over.
咒语
Dedisco.
你不会记得这些的
You won't remember any of this.
这倒也挺诗意化的嘛
That feels poetic, too.
我想我们还是应该讨论一下分寸这个事儿
I think we need to have that chat about boundaries.
你到底做了什么
What the hell did you do?
爸爸
Dad?
我们这是在哪
Where are we?
我们在监狱里的世界
We're in a prison world.
我还以为你说这边的世界会是一样的
I thought you said the worlds would be identical.
这不是今天你们造出的世界
It's not the one you made today.
这是你们小时候的世界
It's-it's the one you made when you were kids.
我们怎么会在这儿
Why are we here?
我想阿莉莎·常是想给我上堂课
I'm guessing Alyssa Chang wants to teach me a lesson.
为什么
For what?
不该这么教导年轻人
The miseducation of young minds.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian?
哈喽  伊丽莎白
Hello, Elizabeth.
真没想到会在这儿见到你
Fancy meeting you here.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）